Guide to the F. Jay Haynes Papers1870-1922bulk 1885-1916
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- Yellowstone Park Stage-Business Records, 3
  - Yellowstone-Western Stage Company, 4
    - Statement of operations and surplus account, 1910-1913 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Income tax statement, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Finances and receipts, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Automobiles in Yellowstone Park, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Agreement for sale of [YW] stock, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Statements and returns, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Chalet Hotel project, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1915 January (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1915 February (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1915 June (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1915 June-September (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1915 October-December (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Transportation concession lease, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Yellowstone park bookings, 1915 February 26 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Tour calendar; Tour bookings, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Tour business material, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Cause of delay of passengers at Yellowstone (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Mrs. Louise Hubscher accident at Thumb, 1915 Sep 9 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Stage and hotel schedule [tour packages] (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Memorandum of YNP travel, season of 1915 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Finances, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Statement of assets; balance sheet, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Financial report, original and corrected copies, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1916 January-April (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1916 May (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1916 June (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1916 July-September (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, transportation passes, 1916 October-December (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Lease contracts, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - FJH's suggestions for motorizing transportation business in YNP (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Proposed YW motor coach, blueline (White body, Hopkins) coachwork, 1916 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Minutes of a meeting of the concessionaire's of Yellowstone Park, with Secretary Albright (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - At a conference of certain concessionaires .... 1916 Dec 10 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - YNP "bookings corrected up to June 27th (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Travel and misc. expenses (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Finances (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Payroll (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Taxes (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Daily route telegrams (Box 23, Folder 1-30)
    - Financial statement (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Stock agreements and contracts (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Special stockholder meeting minutes (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Sales of YW misc. supplies, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - YW barn remodeling contract (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Bills and inventories (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - MY taxes (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - YW taxes (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - YW taxes (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Cheques to Robert Duff; YW Ranch condemnation (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1917 January-February (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1917 March-April (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1917 May-June (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1917 September-December (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1918 January-June (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - YW taxes (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Special use permit (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - YW taxes (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Special use permit (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Equipment sales (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Tax correspondence (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - MY taxes (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - MY taxes (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - YW building lease (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - New York Central Railroad bill (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Special use permit (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - MY dissolution papers and taxes (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - YW dissolution papers and taxes (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Montana & Yellowstone Park Transfer Co. dissolution papers (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Haynes Palace Studio Car floor plan (blueline drawing) (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - YNP Ground lease (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Cody-Sylvan Pass Motor Company, 5
    - Cody Gateway to Yellowstone Park Memorandum for Year 1916. (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Deposition of Mr. Kelly of White [Motor] Co regarding autos in Yellowstone Park (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Stockholders' meeting minutes (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Financial statements and audit (Box 22, Folder 32)